welcome back it's Dr sji hi I'm Ellie
she's been practicing Aesthetics for
what over a decade right yeah over 10
years now um so she knows everything
there is about skin she sees a lot of
the patients that walk through the doors
at Dr man spa and one of the we've got a
treat for you today and the treat is
we're going to actually review a medical
skincare brand only available to buy
from a clinic or someone with suitable
knowledge about skin so it's going to be
a review of Z
Z stands for zeni um this is a US based
dermatologist uh who originally made uh
aaji which I'm a big fan of uh nudum
which is a great it's great very simple
skincare routine like for pigmentation
and it has actually ingredients that
work so like tretinoin um hydroquinone
is one of them uh slightly controversial
um but it's very very effective so he
wanted to create another brand and zedo
came about so there's so many different
products within this range it's used a
lot there are some good things about the
range and there are some things that are
not so good um and we're going to talk
to you about well if you do go to
clinics how to choose the right products
for you and what to be careful of when
you're looking at different products so
we're going to go through our top 10
cells um so the skin care that sells the
best at my clinics and we're going to
break down each product and it's going
to be essentially a very honest review
of the brand um I really like zedo um I
feel like it's a a brand that does
deliver the results um it gets my client
skin ready before I get them in for
clinical treatments um and to be honest
when I send them away with that prepack
I know that they're going to come back
already with results I think it's good
for lots of skin types acne it helps
with anti-aging pigmentation yeah and
even some cases of rosoa so and what
sort of problems have you had with it in
K sometimes people become a little bit
sensitive if it's too aggressive right
um but I feel like I feel like they have
to just be on the the lower form of it
and just sort of go for it nice and
slowly and build theirself up people get
a little bit ahead of theirself and
might use too much of the product too
quickly and they don't listen um so
maybe they might get excessive dry dry
peely skin but then we just take it back
again and reintroduce juice and actually
H being okay so here's the number one
product that we sell at a clinic it's
the oil control pads so who do you use
this for in in a clinic um a typically
an acne skin type someone who's
excessively oily um a combination skin
type um if we're wanting to reduce the
oil reduce the pore size um the oil
control pads are great a great way of
ton in so like I mean just with with
pads alone obviously in terms of
environmental things it's not too good
is it but I mean oil control pads these
are really really popular with people
with acne um if we look at the inky list
we look at some of the active
ingredients you've got the salicylic
acid which uh is great for the skin it's
got mandelic acid which I like yeah and
why do you like the mandelic acid
because um compared to the other toner
where this one's got the additional
mandelic I feel like it's quite calming
and soothing and typically a lot of the
acne patients that we see they come in
with a lot of inflammation so I like
that it's got that mandelic just to
suppress that okay perfect and it's got
some grapefruit extracts in there so Ros
can liner fruit extract some wood
extract as well just hoping maybe even
with some kind of like brightening and
lightninging ingredients um but you know
there are some things over here in the
ingredient list that are a little bit
you know here and there so like they've
got some witch hazel which sometimes for
like rosacea patients is not too good it
can make rosacea a little bit worse so
if you have rosacea you got to have a
bit of caution with this product um even
though it's got the mandelic acid um and
unfortunately for for a medical brand
it's unfortunate that obviously they've
got quite a high content of alcohol in
there um which can kind of desensitize
the skin and strip it and dry and strip
it and dry it and and it could be too
stripping and too drying um and then
lower down in the formula they've also
got some fragrance and perfume in there
which again is slightly disappointing
because they did add like lemon and
LOLOL in there which help with that sort
of lemony fresh feel including those two
ingredients can even sensitize the skin
but having perfume and alcohol is a
really bad mix so if you've previously
suffered from like an impair Skin
Barrier or previously had sensitive skin
this is not going to be a good thing and
it's maybe something that you only use
very for short term so if you have like
a really kind of small little breakout
and you want to control it this is what
I would use but you know how I feel
about kind of fragrance and stuff in
skare I'm not a fan of it so okay number
two is the radical Night Repair that's
is a 1% retinol right okay so from the
nose that urine it's uh it's it improves
skin appearance bright and smooth any
texture it's got microencapsulated
retinol in there so like 1% retinol
sounds really strong to people why does
do people get irritated with this or is
it no I would tend to give this to
someone um they're a little bit on the
sensitive side well not sensitive but
they're like maybe like new to retinol
and I want to build them up because
actually where it's microencapsulated it
means it's slowly released into the skin
um so you get not as much irritation so
actually I think it's quite a gentle way
of getting you on AAL so actually and I
mean it's got so many other vitamins in
there it's got vitamin c e a so like if
you're using a very strong retinol then
you'd use like another sandwich method
you'd use possibly something hydrophilic
just underneath so hyaluronic acid then
you might use a retinol over the top of
that and then you might use something to
help with a Skin Barrier as well so
there are a number of different things
that obviously we recommend um this
formulation is pretty good on the face
of it because obviously you've got a
mixture of 1% retinol um good like
vitamin C's E's um as well as help
things to help with the Skin Barrier so
some great oils as well MH um and you
know I think it's got those sort of
plant stem cells in there so is a great
all arounded an antioxidant for like
kind of aging and Fine Lines right do
you find it kind of like Smooths very
well over the skin yeah I find
deprication is quite nice and it absorbs
in very nicely I mean there's no
surprise because obviously the first few
ingredients are actually silicone so
it's mainly silicon based um so like you
know silicone again is not great for the
environment it doesn't bgrade um it's
it's generally non-comedogenic if you
look at a lot of articles but we find
that sometimes with product some
individuals with silicone it does block
pores it can congest a little bit so you
got to be a little bit careful you're
particularly acne prone or you're very
sensitive in skin type then you got to
be very careful um and then you've got
the sweet almond oil which is part of a
lot of products nowadays which is um
really good for the Skin Barrier
glycerin which is fantastic retinol is
quite High out in the inul so it's a
good strong concentration but we knew
that anyway and they've got a lot of
great ingredients that will help with
that Skin Barrier um including obviously
coming a little bit lower down the
vitamin C as well as Vitamin E which is
great um but again you know what lets it
down is that it's this fragrance in here
again so you know this is a very strong
retinol
formulation and you'd rather it not
smell great yeah rather than adding
perfume into it because you're going to
stimulate that immune system stimulate
that inflammatory Cascade and then you
may have a bad association with with
perfuming products now people always
perfume's good perfume's not well look
if you've got sensitive skin it's going
to be a bad thing we use perfume in a
number of different products in a daily
basis for example our hair shampoo but
these are not leave on things you wash
it off this is something you're going to
leave on overnight so I would exercise
quite a bit of caution if you have
sensitive skin impaired skin barrier or
rosacea with this product okay so the
next product again no surprise is the r
are the retinol skin brighteners now um
I've seen you uh give a lot of patients
this um why do you like those those sort
of three products that you've got within
this range um I like this retinor cuz I
feel like it helps to um clear the
complexion and lower pigmentation um and
I like it that it comes in different
strengths it's just not one so you can
build it up slowly so we've talked about
this in our previous retinol videos the
ability to be able to kind of slowly
increase it so go up the ladder and then
you get more benefits from it so you've
got like a 0.25 0.5 and a 1% over here
um so what's different from this retinol
to the other retinol that we talked
about just before um I typically find
that people don't get as much downtime
with these ones um so yeah I find
obviously we do start them one the 0.25
and build up like that so I like the
fact that they don't get as much IR
irritation from designed to be a little
bit more milder and we'll have a look at
it so it's a water-based um waterbased
thing so it spread easily you've got the
silicone in there the sweet almond oil
which is great you know ceral alcohol
was great for the um Skin Barrier so
it's a good alcohol um and yes we've got
uh apricot kernel oil so it's a lot more
soothing a lot more friendly to the skin
um some lavender oil in there which is
fantastic you've got the retinol you do
have some alcohol in there which again
is a little bit so anything with kind
any simple alcohols and skincare can be
inh irritant it's great people include
alcohol to try and improve the efficacy
of the ingredients but there are other
ways around it now there's actually
non-alcohol versions of like ingredient
enhancers that you can use and what's
really nice with this product is you've
got a few great ingredients so you've
got glutathione which um we do in like
IV DPS at the clinic and that helps with
like brightening um improving the tone
of the skin so like you said Lely glow
with that yeah so glutathion is a
fantastic ingredient that's over here
you've also got some biku oil which is
what I always say is um if you want to
lower the retinol concentration in the
product and you still want efficacy
without it being so drying you include
Biko in there balances it yeah and in my
own skincare I've done exactly the same
because just including retinol alone at
a very Optimum dosage can be a little
bit drying so this product is obviously
designed to be less kind of drying and a
little bit more let's say more baby
steps and more kinder to the skin gentle
way of doing and you don't want to get
to be peeling you retinoid reactions are
not good especially if you've got
perfuming products so you know the only
products that I would use that have
perfuming other ones that are a little
bit more milder but as we come down into
this product let's have a look we got
babalo all great things for the Skin
Barrier really to be honest um and
you've got some LOLOL and lemine but
there's no perfume in this particular
product so you know this is actually one
that I probably would recommend because
yes it's got some silicon you know
obviously a lot of skare Brands don't
seem to care for like the environment
and stuff but um it's got some some
Citrus things in there which can
sensitize but they're much less than
perfumes it's got some alcohol in there
but it's not terrible so if there's one
that I sort of recommend in terms of
retinol I'd probably recommend this cuz
this is not going to desensitize your
skin as quick as some of the other
formulations definitely next product
we're going to talk about is one of my
personal favorites which is the wrinkle
text repair 0 .5% retinol I really love
this product um cuz I just feel it
delivers results it does what it says
it's brilliant for Fine Lines wrinkles
but even deeper lines and wrinkles too
the Z core complex is a really um good
one because it drives the product deeper
into the skin so you're actually going
to hit the skin on the epidermis but
also in the dermal layer all right so
does it mean that this is stronger than
the other retinols out there or is it
pack a bigger punch H I think it packs a
bit bigger punch
um and I think it is more aggressive
because you do get a lot of downtime
with this product so you do definitely
have to build it up slowly so let's have
a look because this is your favorite one
so you're going to stand a test of the
ingredients to see if there's anything
naughty in there so um it's a waterbased
um serum it's got some good things for
the Skin Barrier the SEO alcohol AO
alcohol is great the kernel AIC kernel
oil lavender oil all great you got some
great antioxidant oils with the
pelagonian gravan flower oil which is
great for anti-inflammatory properties
as well then you got the retinol pretty
much in the middle of the list so you
know it's still a good a good
concentration so 0.5 is probably about
correct um as we come down some great
little small peptide complex so I think
this is what they're referring to when
they're talking about um being able to
deliver it a bit deeper down um so
simply just some peptides within there
which is great and as you come down
you've got the linol loline you know
kind of Citrus complex which you know is
not like I said is not terrible it is a
little bit sensitizing if you want a
completely clean brand but this all in
all is is is a decent you know kind of
Inky list over here so you know it's
quite clear that they can create
something that's not too sensitizing but
this one is probably one that I would go
for because I'd say Yes um you know and
that's probably the reason why you seen
such good results with your patients
because it's not going to sensitize you
it might be quite strong but in terms of
it delivery but it's a retinol works
yeah so therefore this product works and
in terms of retinol is this more for
like acne is it for anti-aging or I
would definitely say it's more like
anti-aging or even people when they have
that like textured skin post acne right
it's really good for so for like acne
scarring and stuff it's a really useful
great product yeah anything texture um
lines wrinkles um but it's also got that
Z zpr in there so it does actually
restore the barrier function so it's not
it's quite hydrating okay at the same
time and then this is the one that had
like the broccoli extract in there right
yeah yeah what does that do the broccoli
extract I think that helps to just calm
um calm the skin down yeah so it's like
a like a anti sort of like irritant IR
because it is quite and I think that's
quite that's quite a quite a novel thing
like you've got retinol and you're
balancing it up with something that you
know kind of just stops the irritation I
think that's quite nice it's a nice
little combination so the next product
is the most popular eye cream that we
sell and you know I kind of Stand by
this product as well um I think it's
generally a clean product we'll look at
the inky but um it's the growth factor I
serum so we actually don't have any in
stock no we never have any stocks if it
comes in it goes straight out it's gone
so off for so we actually don't have any
to show you today but you've got you use
it yourself at home right yes I so so
how why do you like using and what does
it do for you I really like using this
product because I suffer with a lot of
dehydration so it's very uh hydrating
it's very hydrophilic um I find that it
just plumps out my little fine lines and
wrinkles it's great for anti-aging yeah
um and it's also um good for like dark
circles CU you've got that lymphatic
cooling tip on it oh wow okay it's
really nice cuz you can just do some
little lymphatic drainage as you're
applying it as well I mean that's a
really important thing with eyes is this
kind of depuffing yes um just helping
with fine lines and wrinkles and uh it's
got that sort of neuropeptide in there
right so neuropeptide is going to give
you a mild like botox effect so it's
going to relax the wrinkles so patients
that have like botox and stuff they use
that and it just enhances the results
right um and then the other thing is
like you mentioned it's got It's really
hydrophilic so it's got the sodium
hyaluronate in there um and it sort of
fills those creases and stuff which is
Fant plumps it up it's got to be one of
the most sophisticated formulas out
there I mean if you're looking at the
ingredient list yeah you've got the
silicone in there but that helps with
the smoothness we've already talked
about the advantages and disadvantages
of silicone um but you've got glycerin
base so that's the reason why it's it
really kind of helps with the barrier
really hydrating not drying at all you
got the wheat germ oil all of these
things are great for people with like in
impaired skin barriers and you've got
some great plant extracts which are
really useful in terms of like helping
the Skin's natural function um and as
you come down there's nothing really
terrible I mean obviously we've got
different types of silicone there to
really help it spread but that's going
to give you that hydration within that
area it's it's almost got the same type
of ingredients that you could need for
like a scar cream that's how much
silicone there is in there um but you
know have you looking at all of these
kind of like emons and skin barriers
things have have you ever seen anyone
with like getting milia or anything like
that afterwards or using this product or
no no not yet no so it's you know it's
not it's not Gomen it's not going to
block anything within that area it's
quite a smooth light formula it is very
light consistency yeah it's very silky
yeah perfect and I mean look like I said
it's it's got both sodium hyaluronate in
there which is the hydrophilic and then
it's got the emoon which is the gold
standard in retaining moisture and then
you've got that cooling tip which some
people say you keep it in the fridge
right yes it's nice and cool when it
goes onely is that recommended by the
company to do that or um no I think
that's just something we like that's uh
yeah so you might want to check with CLE
but we recommend that and I think it's
quite nice actually to keep it in the
fridge it cools things down especially
if you wake up with look kind of puffy
eyes one thing I don't think is going to
help with is pigmentation under under
your eyes cuz there's nothing here in
terms of the ingredients that's really
there for like pigmentation concerns so
if you've got puffy eyes or you've got
fine around the eyes it's a great
product um and it really helps if you've
had like other treatments and facials
and things like that it enhances it but
it's not going to help with pigmentation
no so the next one is an exfoliant so
it's the exfoli wait the exfoliating
polish This Is What It Is by Zena Bari
now you said off camera that you like
this I do I love so who do you prescribe
this for um this generally is for all
skin types actually but I I tend to give
it more to um oily skin type
um
anti-aging uh
combination and pigmentation so quite a
lot so you wouldn't give it to someone
with dry skin right no no I tend to get
them on the rest of the range and then I
I would eventually introduce them into
this but I would maybe like down the
line May down the line okay fine I mean
look so key ingredients what are the key
things that are working here that are
doing the job the the Magnesium crystals
okay so they are is that like a chemical
exfoliant or is it like a physical
physical okay and I know sometimes we
you know we don't really like the
physical uh chemical physical ones I
mean the physical ones that we don't
like physical ones that we can see right
but these are like really ultra fine
crystals they're almost akin to having
like demob brasion or safely so you
don't want to really scrub too much like
what's how how long should they be
should they be polishing a skin you
would apply onto a damp skin and then
you would just lightly like massage it
in and they actually um melt yeah almost
yeah um and then you just take that off
after like maybe like 30 seconds of
doing it and then rinsing it off okay
fine and that's after you're cleansing
and all that sort of stuff right okay
fine and then what about the kind of
actives that are in there um so the
actives with the exfoliating polish
you've got the vitamin C you've got
vitamin A and youve got vitamin E in
there which is quite a nice added extra
so youve got the ace formula essentially
which is what what I always say is a
great formula for everything because
obviously you got the vitamin A the
retinol that's going to help with
collagen stimulation help keep acne and
Bay got the vitamin C which is your skin
care rounder reducing pigmentation
reducing redness a great antioxidant and
then you're sealing that with vitamin E
to make sure that your skin barri is
functioning well those are all tips for
essentially glowing skin um now if we
look at the ingredient list we can see
there's magnesium oxide so that's
obviously those little crystals that
you're talking about um just to add on
that as well cuz normally I don't
actually like physical cool scrubs but
with this one because they're they're
crystals if you looked at them under a
lamp they're fully round so they don't
actually scratch so they so they've got
round Edge basically okay that's a
that's that's a good point um so you got
some paraffin in there mineral oil um
you know there can be a little bit that
can clog up skin a little bit mineral
oil sometimes um you've got the linol
oil you've got uh perfume in there which
is not good so I I can't recommend it
now but uh you got the linol and you've
got retinol palmitate so it's a very low
strength it's very light retinol
palmitate is on the lowest ladder of the
retinoid Lou ladder but it's a great
starter so someone wants to maybe like
introduce themselves to retinol that
might not be a bad thing um and then
you've got Tetra heex score bit so it's
actually good quality vitamin C stable
vitamin C that's sitting there so you
know there's a lot of evidence here that
you should probably once you put it on
it might be beneficial to probably even
leave on the product for a good like 5
10 minutes before watching off um is
there anything that you've ever tried or
um I haven't but I'm going I'm going to
True
see um so you know maybe that's a top
tip there but I think there's obviously
there there is some evidence because you
you don't want to wash some of this
stuff off so quickly I think um um to
reap the benefits you want to reap the
benefits and you know that's one things
that I like about like polishes and
things that you can use it as a
temporary mask sometimes yeah so the
next product that we're going to talk
about from Z is the exfoliating cleanser
from for normal to oily skin types okay
so those are the people that You' use it
right so bit more of exfoliation is it a
bit more aggressive then then the then
something like the Polish or a lot less
aggressive a lot less so it's just
gentle basically yeah yeah so this one
um is obviously great for oily skin
types and it just helps to get rid of
that surface uh buildup of oil you still
use it with your exfoliating polish
after all right okay fine um but you or
your other polish or your other um
exfoliant but you would use this as your
cleanser as your first stage Okay cool
so this is the first stage this is what
you do and then if you want extra stuff
then you'll add the exfoliating polish
afterwards so this is like it doesn't
strip the skin is it a physical
exfoliant is it chemical exfoliant so it
has it does have the little beads in
there but they actually dissolve on the
skin and they actually feel really nice
all right okay so it just like Foams up
Bally it Foams up yeah you've got the
gel it's a gel base um and it Foams up
lava that you rinse it off and it just
leaves the skin feeling really nice and
clear and just reduces that surface oil
and the key ingredients over here you've
got um I can never say it right but hoba
that's pretty good hoba Esters in there
so that helps to explorate the dead skin
sets okay fine and one thing that really
interested me was the cuz we know about
encapsulated retinol but why the
encapsulated vitamin E in this product
um it just helps give the the skin more
of an antioxidant benefit but just like
slowly yeah don't know why I don't know
why maybe someone from Zeta just write
it in the comments
below let's have a look at the
ingredients list um so here we are so
we've got this hoba um essers which is
fantastic like you said got a few good
extracts which are really nice nice
cinnamide great for the Skin Barrier big
tick there then you got some salicylic
acid so it's really nice allrounder
obviously I'm I'm going to tell you what
happens lower down because you know it's
the running theme the perfume and and
and some desensitizing things which is
are not great but you know I think that
if you've got like decent sort of normal
skin with not much sensitivity maybe the
OD break out here and then and you want
to improve your complexion and glow then
this is not a bad sort of exfoliating
cleanser would you use this every day or
would you use it or you use it every day
morning and night morning and night so
you exfoliate morning and night yeah
it's it's not an aggressive exfoliat
it's quite mild it's quite I guess with
the niin the vitamin E and everything in
there it can be quite soothing as well
it's a bit more soothing so it's
actually one of the rare things that
it's an exfoliating cleans you can use
twice daily yes um I wouldn't leave it
on just because of the perfume and stuff
that we we don't want to sensitize the
skin which is not great um but I think
it's a nice like mild little cleanser it
is good so the next one is the one that
I see all the time in a lot of skare
plans that you make uh it's the day
Power Defense yeah so it's a nice name
for for for for a serum right it is it
is nice and it's a really nice staple I
think throughout all of the the whole
range we always recommend this product
um it's just great for restoring this
the barrier function so you get really
nice hydration with it and it's um helps
with fine lines and wrinkles so it's one
of the few products within this range
that obviously have camide so it's got
camide 6 there that helps restore the
barrier function it's got metrix all
3000 so nice collection of peptides um
would have been nice to have some
different types of metrix on there like
synthetics as well but um you know it's
still got some key ingredients that are
really quite nice so um look I'm looking
at the ingredients over here some good
ingredients glycerin based um really
nice kind of few oils that you were
talking about so the Mandarin orange
peel oil which is really nice citrus
lemon peel oil so all of these things
are really going to help with like kind
of antioxidant properties um and you've
got some I think I saw that there was
some a lot of peptides in there which
was responsible with the metrix 3000
which are great for kind of like
building the skin and helping with
everything so I can understand why you
kind of build a skin care like plan
around this um it's got retinol in there
um it's got retinol palmitate in there
as well so two different types of light
retinol just giving you a little bit of
collagen simulation so it's an all
around thing that even I guess when
people don't have so much problems then
they can still use this quite nicely um
so all in all really nice uh
formulation um and you know not too much
going of wrong with it and and that's
the reason why I think I see a lot of
patients is using that longterm without
any problems um and it's one of the one
of the biggest Sellers and you'd use
that what like a.m. p.m or both uh both
yeah morning and night yeah so that's a
nice stap serum your probably your
favorite all around serum in the range I
do yeah I really like this product and
the reason why we don't have it today is
cuz just sold out
yeah okay fine um so the next one is the
growth factor serum so you like this
growth factor serum right yes I do I
love this product cuz I know that I'm
going to send someone away and they're
going to they're going to get the
results okay what results do they expect
um it really helps to plump out fine
lines wrinkles firming it's very
anti-aging um it's fantastic for
hydration and helps to restore the barer
function as well yeah um so again if
people like that injectables and things
and they want to maintain it in between
this is a great product so this is a
great one that You' pair with the eye
cream that we talked about great very
looking at the thing you've got these uh
the bleer stem cell so it helps prevent
future aging you've got um things uh so
po uh polymorphia sinesis root extract
which helps calms and soothe the skin um
as well as has um the jinang extract
ring jinen extract which helps with
elasticity and firmness and if you
actually look at the ingredients yes
we've got some silicone in there which
is a little bit disappointing um but
those root extracts come up a lot more
higher on the list so it's a very
natural like
plantbased um growth factor
stimulating um serum which is you know
it's pretty much more like sort of like
almost like an is clinical serum isn't
it um it reminds me of one of those
formulations which is a nice brand yeah
and I like it as well because I think
where you can get an good anti-aging um
results with it without having to go
onto an aggressive retinol so if someone
doesn't want to quite go on a retinol
yet this is quite so they do that before
there or they can use it in the day in
between when they're like working up a
retinol or something like that they
could do yeah yeah okay fine and then
the final one um which I think that you
know I see a lot paired with treatments
at the clinic so if you having
treatments in a clinic and you want to
enhance them one of the ones that we
sell a lot of is the Firming Serum yes
so that's got a number of different
benefits it's an anti-aging like
breakthrough in the skin structure and
shapes it's mild lightweight it's a
tolerable formulation indicated for sort
of all skin types um sensitive skin
helps with elasticity firmness and it's
great for um all of those collagen
inducing treatments that you do so like
morphia
softwave like micro needling primx evoke
um and you know I think it's again it's
a plant stem cell based formulation so
one of the things that I like is the
sodium DNA in this because it works
alongside with the skin Matrix um in
terms of stimulating fiber blast
activity so fiber blast what do is it
produce elastin elastin collagen and
elastin so it's that's what you need so
if you're going to have something that's
collagen inducing treatment then
this is going to be the one for you um
if you don't have treatments then you
can probably use some of the other
serums that we mentioned in arrange but
uh you know I think that I see a lot of
patients with like daily Power Defense
in the morning and using the Firming
Serum at night it's a great com so it's
a great combination so there you have it
those are the top 10 products that are
sold at Dr Med SP there's some advantag
and disadvantages with the range I do
think that uh this range is not for
people with very sensitive skin or
people that have allergies or any kind
of
intolerances um it has to be used
cautiously especially with the leave on
products just because of the addition of
alcohol um and fragrance within the
formulations but overall the ingredient
lists are really quite strong there's
some interesting ingredients A Perfect
Blend of kind of like botanically
derived ingredients as well as um things
that are evidence-based and proven to
work and some really like kind of well
ingenious like delivery of things and I
think you know the structured increasing
of the retinol is one of the most
popular things that we see at the clinic
definitely so it's definitely a brand
that delivers results yeah but I would
never use this brand by yourself I would
always I would always have some
professional skin professional to point
you in the right direction because you
need someone that knows skin to be able
to really like say well no stop this use
this use this just once a day alter it
or just stop using this all together and
replace it with this so it requires an
innate knowledge of absolutely
everything going on and I I would say
with zedo you learn something new every
day right you do yeah I mean whenever we
recommend zedo we send a structur plan
and exactly how to use it so there's no
way that you can use it incorrectly okay
perfect thank you so much for listening
guys if you have any questions about any
of those products or any other products
within the zedo range just let us know
in the comments below if you want to see
Ellie in more videos just uh click like
And subscribe because then you'll let
we'll let you know when she's on next
thanks guys bye
[Music]
byebye